Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Editorial files, by title
  - Mademoiselle
    - Manuscripts
      - Artwork charged off, 1944; 1947-1948
        - Photograph for Design for Living of Pat Smart's bedroom with valentine collection, includes note (Box 212)
        - Photographs of Elizabeth Ames by Bunny Adler #15150, includes note (Oversize 10)
        - Photographs of Latin American drawings, includes note; 2 items (Box 212)
        - Photographs of Skipper Ross (2) #14682, includes note (Box 212)
      - All Is Not Glamour That Glitters / Anonymous [Kathryn I. Rickman], copyedited version of original manuscript and 3 re-typed copies of original manuscript incorporating some revision (Box 212)
      - As You Were'nt [sic] / Ruth Chandler Moore, original manuscript with light revisions and 3 re-typed copies of original manuscript incorporating some revision (Box 212)
      - Battle of the Campuses / Gloria and Lucia Snyder (Box 212)
      - The Bicycle Girl / Rion Bercovici (Box 212)
      - Bonnets? God Bless 'Em! / Dorothy Conn [Dorothy P. Conroy], copyedited original manuscript and 2nd and 3rd slightly altered copies of original manuscript (Box 212)
      - Bowling feature / Mignon Bushell McLaughlin, idea in letter form with 2 copies of re-typed manuscript (Box 212)
      - Boy Wanted / Kay Hosking, copyedited original manuscript with 3 copies of revision, galleys (Box 212)
      - Brazilian 'Betty Co-eds' (alternate title: "Brazilian Co-eds") / Helen Randolph and Augusto Rodrigues, original manuscript, lightly revised, and 3 copies of revised manuscript, with notes, photographs (Box 212)
      - California's Women Soldiers / Howard E. Jackson, including photographs (Box 212)
      - Career Girls in Uruguay / Bianca Marvin (Box 212)
      - A Career or Marriage? What's Your Score / Lois Klemm (Box 212)
      - Come, Josephine, in My Flying Machine / Oden and Olivia Meeker (Box 212)
      - Consider the Startled Faun / Ray Buffum, original manuscript, annotated with editorial comments and 3 re-typed copies of manuscript incorporating some revision, with notes (Box 212)
      - Copy on Helen Dettweiler / Jane Haggard, including memorandum, note (Box 212)
      - Data (biographical) on Bonnie Farber / Gretchen Van Tassel, including notecard, photographs (Box 212)
      - Dawn Drama / Evelyn Hart, original manuscript, revised, and a second copy of manuscript incorporating some revisions, with cross reference sheet, layouts for an unrelated manuscript (Box 212)
      - Dear Diary / Katharine Beale, original manuscript and 3 re-typed copies of manuscript, with note (Box 212)
      - Digest of Idea for Photographic Spread / submitted by Roberta Richardson (Box 212)
      - Do Emotional Enemies Wreck Your Days? / Louise May Snyder (Box 212)
      - Do You Love Me or Don't You? / Hildegarde Dolson (Box 212)
      - Don't Marry a Cowboy / Betty Preat Iselin, original manuscript with 3 re-typed copies (Box 213)
      - Feet of Clay Department / Geraldine Sartain, including note (Box 213)
      - Fiesta on a Shoestring / Doris Heydn, copyedited original manuscript, and 4 copies of revised manuscript (Box 213)
      - Foreign Language Jobs for Women / Victor W. Burke[?] (Box 213)
      - Free Woman / Frances Minturn Howard (Box 213)
      - Freshman Dean / Paul Jones (Box 213)
      - From Us to Him / Robert Fontaine (Box 213)
      - Fun in Finance / Pearl Anoe, original manuscript and 2 re-typed copies, with correspondence, notes (Box 213)
      - Good Neighbor / Ann Holmes (Box 213)
      - Good Neighbor Fiesta [title from inventory #3 and old folder heading] / Doris Heydn [Doris Waller] (Box 213)
      - Grandma Never Called It That [alternate title: "Inside Information or I'm So Gland to See You"] / Louise Brandon, original copyedited manuscript with editorial comments, and 3 re-typed copies of manuscript incorporating some revisions (Box 213)
      - Graphology Career Detector / Lucy Stanton, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 213)
      - Gun Girls on the Job / no author (Box 213)
      - Gus and Edith Erker - Ladue Bar Catering Service / no author (Box 213)
      - Hell Bent for Nowhere, or Mrs. Crosby Resents / Kate Sproehnle, including letter (Box 213)
      - How a Woman Can Swing Two Jobs / Mary G. Phillips, including 5 re-typed copies of manuscript, memoranda, notes (Box 213)
      - How Articles Get That Way / Elinore Denniston, including note (Box 213)
      - How to Travel with a Husband / Elizabeth Stafford, includes 3 re-typed copies of manuscript, letter, Skyway luggage catalog (Box 213)
      - I Am a Brazilian / Teddy Hecht [Edwina Baboza-Carneiro?], original manuscript and copy, June 1942 revision, and 3 re-typed copies of revised ms (Box 213)
      - I Am a WAAC / Mera Galloway, including memorandum (Box 213)
      - I Want a Doll for Christmas / Peter Lind Hayes, including memorandum, voucher (Box 213)
      - I Was a Dress / Peggy Sykes, including note (Box 213)
      - I'm Allergic to Health / Henrietta Fort Holland, copyedited manuscript, with 2 sets of galleys (Box 213)
      - In Defense of Vanity / Carola de Peyster Kip (Box 213)
      - Intercollegiate Broadcasting / Andre Emmerich, correspondence, memoranda, notes, issue of IBS Bulletin for Summer 1946, no manuscript (Box 213)
      - Is It Glasses vs. Glamour? / Peggy Gillan, original copyedited manuscript and 2 re-typed copies of revision, with note (Box 213)
      - Jim and Elaine Cannon / no author (Box 213)
      - Job News [title from inventory of manuscripts charged off] / no author, Dec. 31, 1946 (Box 213)
      - Juvenile Writing as a Career / Marian King, original copyedited manuscript and re-typed copy of manuscript (Box 213)
      - The Kidnapping of Anne Vanderham / Ellis Parker Butler (Box 213)
      - Let's Pretend / George R. Pilgrim (Box 213)
      - Look Before You Teach / Cathleen Burns, including note (Box 213)
      - The Lure of the Wilderness / Theodora Stanwell-Fletcher, including notes (Box 213)
      - Mademoiselle Matchmaker / no author, layout materials, no manuscript (Box 213)
      - March Wind / Gladys Taber, copyedited manuscript (Box 213)
      - Married Wave / Alice Martens McHugh, including memoranda, photographs (Box 213)
      - The Masked Ladies of Lima / Jorge Guardia-Berdecio and Peter Jefferson Packer, including 3 re-typed copies of manuscript, illustration (Box 213)
      - Material on Francis Mahier / Harold Rubin, 2 copies of manuscript, with photographs (Box 213)
      - A Matter of Poise / Cornelia Otis Skinner (Box 213)
      - Memorandum re [Red Cross] Humor Spread, Nov. 17, 1941 (Box 214)
      - Music for Madame, publicity, photographs, no manuscript (Box 214)
      - My Old Man / Faith Flagg, including note (Box 214)
      - The National Police Gazette's Editor / Prudencio de Pereda, including additional re-typed copy of manuscript, note, photograph (Box 214)
      - [New Yorker] / Brokaw, partial manuscript (Box 214)
      - No More Opportunities! / Lorena Ann Olmsted, with 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Not-So-White Collars / Margaret Petsch, including letter, and 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Palestine's Young Women / Beatrice Oppenheim (Box 214)
      - Personal Book Shop / Margaret Kane (Box 214)
      - Postscript for Beginner [alternate title: "Your Bid for Success"] / Esther Eberstaat Brooke, original copyedited manuscript and 2 re-typed manuscripts incorporating some revisions, with 2 sets of galleys, note (Box 214)
      - Printing as a Career / Leonora de Lima Andrews, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript, with notes (Box 214)
      - Reno---With No Thought of Divorce / William B. Powell, original copyedited manuscript and 3 re-typed copies, with photographs and page of captions, and companion piece "Vacation in Nevada" / EEB (Box 214)
      - Research material re maid situation / H.B. Harvey, including 3 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 214)
      - The Return of Grace / Frederick Van Ryn, including re-typed copy, letter (Box 214)
      - Road Closed / Lyta Jorgensen, including 2 re-typed copies (Box 214)
      - [Robert] Taylor / Geraldine Sartain, including notes (Box 214)
      - The Sandals That Made Mexico Famous / Betty-Lee Beatty, original copyedited manuscript and 5 copies of manuscript incorporating some revision, with 2 sets of galleys, notes (Box 214)
      - Script-Tease-es / Dorothy Sara [from old folder heading] (Box 214)
      - Service - Deluxe / Mary Helen Hubbell, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript, note (Box 214)
      - Shameful Avery / Lionel Wiggam, including re-typed copy of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Ski article (Travel) [title from inventory of manuscripts charged off / Pati Hill Meservey, including note; Dec. 31, 1948 (Box 214)
      - Skipper Ross / Edwin M. Hunt, including publicity, notes (Box 214)
      - Son and Heir / Merriam Modell, including re-typed copy of manuscript, galleys, note (Box 214)
      - State Rights / Mary Parker, including note (Box 214)
      - Tailor's Dummy / Dorothy Ducas, including note, photographs (Box 214)
      - Ten Little Onguks / Julia Brainard Carson (Box 214)
      - They Also Serve / Margaret Jameson, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Those Ozarks in Arkansas / Martha Barry, original copyedited manuscript and 3 re-typed copies of manuscript, one with layout, source material, cross reference sheet (Box 214)
      - Turtle at the Seashore / Louise Julia Johnsen, copyedited original manuscript and re-typed copy of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Twelve at Eight / Audacia [Bess F. Armstrong?], including 2 sets of galleys, note (Box 214)
      - Two Timing / Esther W.S. Prosser, including 3 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 214)
      - Vice Versa / Oden and Olivia Meeker (Box 214)
      - Visit to a Psychiatrist [title from inventory of manuscripts charged off] / Nancy Battle Palmer, Dec. 31, 1947 (Box 214)
      - Want a Kitten? / Elsie Sara Farr, copyedited original manuscript and with 2 re-typed copies of manuscript, with photograph (Box 215)
      - Wayward Girl / Dorothy Dayton (Box 215)
      - We the Good Neighbors / Piedad Levi Castillo, original manuscript in Spanish, with English translation (Box 215)
      - What a Soldier Thinks of the WAACS / Anonymous (Box 215)
      - What Kind of a Boss Will You Be? / Katherine Johnson (Box 215)
      - Whoa Up, Nellie! / Mildred Gang Hackney, original manuscript with editorial comments, and 3 re-typed copies of manuscript incorporating some revision, with note (Box 215)
      - Why Get Married? And Why Not? / Rosemary Sheehan and David Donovan, no manuscript, idea only (Box 215)
      - Why Some People Fail / I. Luther Purdom (Box 215)
      - Why You Should Not Be a Writer / Lila Hannah Thomson, including 3 re-typed copies (Box 215)
      - A Woman Comes Home / Lee Harriman (Box 215)
      - Woman's Place / Harry Salpeter - with galleys (Box 215)
      - Women Are O.K. But Not to Work For / Lois Whitcomb, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 215)
      - Women Conservationists / Edwin J. Becker (Box 215)
      - Yoicks for Dianas of the Chase / Marta Mantey, original manuscript with editorial comments, and 2 re-typed copies of manuscript incorporating some revision, with note (Box 215)
      - Young America Designs / Sibilla Skidelsky, including cross reference sheet, note (Box 215)
      - A Young Woman Who Makes Money from Spiders / Edwin Baird, including 2 re-typed copies of manuscript (Box 215)
      - Untitled fiction fragment, p. 7-23 (Box 215)
      - Photographs of paintings executed by different artists of women / Various photographers, 5items (Box 215)
    - Rights information, Feb. 1961-July 1972 (Box 215)
    - Tables of Contents, Feb 1935-Dec 1953; 5 folders (Box 215)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan 1954-Feb 1963; Feb 1966-Aug 1972; 6 folders (Box 216)
  - Mademoiselle's Living (combines records for Living for Young Homemakers)
    - Manuscripts
      - Inventories of art and manuscripts charged off, 1948 (Box 216)
      - California Beach House / Fay Becket, including galleys, layout dummy, page proofs, photographs; 4 folders (Box 216)
      - Gifts photos (from inventory) voucher #13207, includes note (Box 216)
      - The Huckleberry Hill Story / Stanley Mills Haggart, includes captions, illustration, correspondence, invoice, layout dummy, notes, and additional manuscripts for "We Live on Huckleberry Hill" / Helen Leopold (Box 216)
      - King Weese still life photos (8, from inventory) voucher #13177 (Box 216)
      - Kitty Perkins photos (2) and contact sheet (from inventory) voucher #12430, includes note (Box 217)
      - Montalvo Art Foundation story / Rita Davidson, no manuscript, correspondence, memorandum (Box 217)
      - Panel House photos (5, from inventory) voucher #14658, includes note (Box 217)
      - Pick a Card (from inventory) voucher #14674, captions, galleys, layout (Box 217)
    - Tables of Contents, Autumn 1947-Nov. 1961; 5 folders (Box 217)
  - Magnet Detective Library, See Nick Carter titles.
  - Magnet Library, See Nick Carter titles.
  - Modern Girl Stories, See Live Girl Stories.
  - Mystery Magazine, See Crime Busters.
  - Mystery Story Magazine, See Crime Busters.
  - National Magazine, See Street & Smith's National Magazine.
  - New Buffalo Bill Weekly (combines records for Western Story Magazine; Street & Smith's Western Story Magazine)
    - Manuscripts purchase cards, Jan 1926-Dec 1929; 4 folders (Box 217)
    - Manuscripts purchase cards, Jan 1930-Oct 1938; 9 folders (Box 218)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1938-Feb 1938 (Box 218)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Mar 1938-Feb 1940; 12 folders (Box 219)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Mar 1940-Dec 1941; 11 folders (Box 220)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1942-Dec 1944; 14 folders (Box 221)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1945-Mar 1949; 13 folders (Box 222)
    - Manuscripts
      - Inventories of art and manuscripts charged off and memoranda, 1933-1946 (Box 222)
      - Memorandum of Lifted Stories Used in Western Story Magazine (Box 222)
      - Advice to Photographers / Clyde C. Belknap, 2 parts (Box 222)
      - Cowboys---and Hearts / Stephen A.D. Cox (Box 222)
      - The Curse of the Black Death / Reginald C. Barker (Box 222)
      - The 11th (Eleventh) Hour / W.S. [or A.?] Wolf, pp. 1-85; with note (Box 222)
      - The 11th (Eleventh) Hour / W.S. [or A.?] Wolf, pp. 86-255; with note; 2 folders (Box 223)
      - A Horse in the Family / Lynne Raven (Box 223)
      - Margate / Frederick Faust, from card index; a.k.a. Nicholas Silver, Max Brand (Box 223)
      - Marshall's Death Brand / Kent Bennett (a.k.a. W.E. Carleton, J.L. Considine?), includes 2 vouchers, partial page proof (Box 223)
      - The Saddle Dude [alternate titles "The Big Auger of Bar ?"; "The Mail Order Ranch King"] / George Gilbert (Box 223)
      - Western Wild Flowers / D.C. Hubbard, 4parts (Box 223)
      - When the Cub Came to the Bear Cat / James Edward Hungerford (Box 223)
      - The White Mouse / George Owen Baxter [a.k.a. Max Brand] (Box 223)
      - Illustration proofs for art charged off, Dec. 31, 1946; 6items (Box 223)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan 1930-Dec 1932; 3 folders (Box 223)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan 1933-Dec 1937; 5 folders (Box 224)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan 1938-Dec 1942; 6 folders (Box 225)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan 1943-Aug/Sep 1949; 6 folders (Box 226)
  - New Magnet Library, See Nick Carter titles.
  - New Nick Carter Library, See Nick Carter titles.
  - New Nick Carter Weekly (New York, N.Y. 1897), See Nick Carter titles.
  - New Nick Carter Weekly (New York, N.Y. 1903), See Nick Carter titles.
  - Nick Carter Radio Series, See Nick Carter titles.
  - Nick Carter titles (combines records for New Nick Carter Library; New Nick Carter Weekly (New York, N.Y. 1897); Nick Carter Weekly; New Nick Carter Weekly (New York, N.Y. 1903); Magnet [Detective] Library; New Magnet Library; Nick Carter Radio Series)
    - Magnet [Detective] Library manuscripts
      - List of Nick Carter's [sic] in stock undated (Box 226)
      - List of Stories Published and to Be Published in Magnet Library (Box 226)
      - Notes,miscellaneous (Box 226)
    - New Magnet Library manuscripts, "revisions of Nick Carters by St. George Rathborne"
      - Labels, notes (Box 226)
      - 928 "The Great Enigma" (Box 226)
      - 938 "Nick Carter and the Greengoods Men" (Box 226)
      - 940 "Tracked Across the Atlantic" (Box 226)
      - 944 "The Great Money-Order Swindle" (Box 226)
      - 946 "A Wall Street Haul" (Box 226)
      - 948 "Sealed Orders" (Box 226)
      - 952 "Fighting Against Millions" (Box 226)
      - 954 "The Old Detective's Pupil" (Box 226)
      - 956 "The Mysterious Mail Robbery" (Box 226)
      - 958 "A Fair Criminal" (Box 226)
      - 960 "The Piano Box Mystery" (Box 226)
      - 962 "A Millionaire Partner" (Box 226)
      - 966 "The Double Shuffle Club" (Box 226)
      - 970 "At Thompson's Ranch" (Box 226)
      - 974 "An Accidental Password" (Box 226)
      - 978 "A Clever Celestial" (Box 226)
      - 980 "Gideon Drexel's Millions" (Box 226)
      - 982 "A Stolen Identity" (Box 226)
      - 983 "Evidence by Telephone" (Box 226)
      - 986 "Lady Velvet" (Box 226)
      - 987 "Playing a Bold Game" (Box 226)
      - 988 "A Dead Man's Ghost" (Box 226)
      - 990 "A Deposit Vault Puzzle" (Box 226)
      - 991 "The Crescent Brotherhood" (Box 226)
      - 994 "Wanted by Two Clients" (Box 226)
      - 995 "The Van Alstine Case" (Box 226)
      - 996 "Check No. 777" (Box 227)
      - 999 "The Sign of the Crossed Knives" (Box 227)
      - 1004 "Caught in the Toils" (Box 227)
      - 1010 "The Gamblers' Syndicate" (Box 227)
      - 1011 "A Chance Discovery" (Box 227)
      - 1012 "Among the Counterfeiters" (Box 227)
      - 1014 "At Odds with Scotland Yard" (Box 227)
      - 1016 "Found on the Beach" (Box 227)
      - 1018 "The Detective's Pretty Neighbor" (Box 227)
      - 1038 "Man Against Man" (Box 227)
      - 1047 "The Man of Iron" (Box 227)
      - 1065 "The Price of a Secret" (Box 227)
      - 1074 "Behind a Mask" (Box 227)
      - 1078 "Run to Earth" (Box 227)
      - Inventory of series #1187-1369, 1926-1933; photocopies (Box 227)
    - Nick Carter Radio Series
      - Memoranda on scripts and notes, 1945; 1964,; undated (Box 227)
      - Inventory/packing material notes for "Nick Carter Triplet" and Nick Carter Weekly #683-4-5" (Box 227)
    - Nick Carter Triplet manuscript
      - A Strange Turning; or Nick Carter and the G.A.R. Badge / W. Bert Foster, 3 folders (Box 227)
    - Nick Carter Weekly #683-4-5 manuscripts
      - Playing a Shrewd Game; or Patsy and the French Detective / W. Bert Foster (Box 227)
      - The Signet of the Dagger; or Nick Carter and Reynard in Partnership / W. Bert Foster (Box 227)
      - Solving a Cable Puzzle [alternate titles A Dash for the Coal"; "The Mystic Mark"; Chick Carter and Reynard, the Mystery"] / W. Bert Foster (Box 227)
    - Other manuscripts
      - The Dog That Became an Elephant; or Nick Carter in Deepening Waters, packing labels and notes (Box 227)
      - The Dog That Became an Elephant; or Nick Carter in Deepening Waters, pp. 1-167; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - The Dog That Became an Elephant; or Nick Carter in Deepening Waters, pp. 168-243 (Box 228)
      - The Wild Women; or Nick Carter and the Manufactured Evidence, 3 folders (Box 228)
    - Nick Carter-related
      - Correspondence, 1912; 1938 (Box 228)
  - Nick Carter Weekly, See Nick Carter titles.
  - People's, See People's Magazine.
  - People's Favorite Magazine, See People's Magazine.
  - People's Ideal Fiction Magazine, See People's Magazine.
  - People's Magazine (combines records for People's Ideal Fiction Magazine; People's; People's Favorite Magazine)
    - Manuscripts
      - Inventories of manuscripts (Box 228)
      - By the Breadth of a Hair / Elizabeth Strong Worthington (Box 228)
      - The Climax / Geoffrey Harris [a.k.a. Edwin Bliss?], includes note (Box 228)
      - The End of the Search / Ellis Paul [a.k.a. Edwin Bliss?], includes note (Box 228)
      - The Treasuries of Kings / R.H. Poole, includes note (Box 228)
    - Tables of Contents, Jan. 1923-Aug. 1924 (Box 228)
  - Pic (New York, N.Y.) (combines records for Pic Quarterly; Street & Smith's All Star Sports)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Oct 1944-Sep 1946; 5 folders (Box 228)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Oct 1946-Sep 1949; 9 folders (Box 229)
    - Manuscripts
      - Inventories of manuscripts and art charged off, 1945; undated (Box 229)
      - Biography of Celeste Holm - text, "from Harry Brand," with 21 photographs, memorandum (Box 229)
      - Blue Book Models - photos only, 7 photographs (Box 229)
      - Cart Art in Italy - text, 23 photographs, Francis C. Fuerst (Box 229)
      - Crime Laboratory That Travels at 60 Miles an Hour, text, 13 photographs "Globe Feature" (Box 229)
      - Dan Dailey, a Lucky Hoofer, layout and photographs (5) (Oversize 11)
      - Ghost Towns, text, 19 photographs "Gunther-Frost for Pic" (Box 229)
      - Gorillas, background and captions, W. Bridges; 19 photographs, Arthur Sasse (Box 229)
      - Hollywood Comes to Us, text, 40 photographs, 9 contact prints (Box 230)
      - Jimmy Wong Howe, photographs (16) (Box 230)
      - Miracle Mould Still Mystery, text, Haskell Cohen, 10 photographs (Box 230)
      - Movies at War Will Help to Build the Peace, text, 19 photographs, Lucien Aigner (Box 230)
      - Some Helpful Hints, in Season, to Hay Fever Victims, text, Albert Deutsch, 12 photographs (Box 230)
      - Summer Resorts Don't Hibernate, text, ??? photographs "Gunther-Frost for Pic" (Box 230)
      - Tennessee Gun Maker, text "from Warner Ogden", 10 photographs (Box 230)
      - Tricks, 12 photographs (Box 230)
      - Unusual Postal Route, text, 15 photographs "Globe Feature" (Box 230)
      - Art charged off, Dec. 31, 1948 (Box 230)
        Kodachromes of the California homes of Whitney Bolton (3), Lucille Bremer (1), Joan Leslie (2), Janis Paige (1), Esther Williams (1)
        Kodachrome of fashions (1)
        Photographs of Don Ameche's home (1), home of unidentified person (1), and various California construction sites (14)
      - Watercolor and ink, "Broadway" #13690, note on back: "Artist in Charm Magazine 3/48-8/48 - 7/48 pg. 56" (Oversize 11)
    - Tables of Contents, Sept. 1945-Spring 1951; 3 folders (Box 230)
  - Pic Quarterly, See Pic (New York, N.Y.).
  - Picture-Play Magazine, See Picture-Play Weekly.
  - Picture-Play (New York, N.Y. 1926), See Picture-Play Weekly.
  - Picture Play (New York, N.Y. 1938), See Picture-Play Weekly.
  - Picture-Play Weekly (combines records for Picture-Play Magazine; Picture-Play (New York, N. Y. 1926); Street & Smith's Picture Play; Picture Play (New York, N.Y. 1938); Your Charm; Charm)
    - Manuscripts purchase cards, 1926 (Box 230)
    - Manuscripts purchase cards, 1927-Sep 1938; 11 folders (Box 231)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1938-Jun 1939; 4 folders (Box 231)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jul 1939-Dec 1945; 13 folders (Box 232)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1946-Dec 1955; 13 folders (Box 233)
    - Manuscripts vouchers, Jan 1956-Aug 1959; 4 folders (Box 234)
    - Manuscripts
      - Inventories of manuscripts charged off and memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 234)
      - Alteration Job / Virginia Earle and Romilda Dilley, includes layout, including illustration, payment note (Box 234)
      - Be Your Own U.S.O. [alternate title: "You Can Be Your Own U.S.O"] / Norton Hughes Jonathan, includes letters, 2 versions of manuscript, layout (Box 234)
      - Beauty on the Battlefront / Dorothy Emerson White (Box 234)
      - Between the Wooing and the Wedding / M. Hayden (Box 234)
      - The Black Pearl / Grace B. Martin, 2 versions (Box 234)